Guide to the Warren Platner Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project Records
  - Yale University: Mathematics Building Competition, 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 164)
    - Photographs (Box 80)
    - Slides (Box 80)
    - Negatives (Box 80)
  - Yale University: David S. Ingalls Rink
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Slides (Box 80)
  - Yuen, Justin
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Photographs (Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified projects
    - Photographs (Box 80)
    - Slides (Box 80)